from database import database
database=database()

ch1=[
    {
        "question": "How many circles do you see",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "9",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which shape in the animation is coloured in green",
        "optionA": "circle",
        "optionB": "square",
        "optionC": "triangle",
        "optionD": "rectangle",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the smallest animal from the picture",
        "optionA": "Elephant",
        "optionB": "Mouse",
        "optionC": "Rabbit",
        "optionD": "Horse",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the biggest fruit in the picture",
        "optionA": "Watermelon",
        "optionB": "Mango",
        "optionC": "Apple",
        "optionD": "Banana",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Select the square from the group",
        "optionA": "1",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "3",
        "optionD": "4",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    }
]


ch2=[
    {
        "question": "How many flowers do you see in the garden",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "9",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many balloons is Manoj holding",
        "optionA": "7",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the biggest number from the group",
        "optionA": "9",
        "optionB": "5",
        "optionC": "6",
        "optionD": "1",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people can you see on the vehicle",
        "optionA": "6",
        "optionB": "7",
        "optionC": "2",
        "optionD": "1",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which object in the picture is in groups of 6",
        "optionA": "Milk Glasses",
        "optionB": "Leaves",
        "optionC": "Potatoes",
        "optionD": "Ants",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    }
]

ch3=[
    {
        "question": "Ravi has 3 balloons, Rani gives Ravi 2 more balloons, how many balloons does Ravi have now",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "9",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ravi has 3 balloons, Rani gives Ravi 4 more balloons, how many balloons does Ravi have now",
        "optionA": "7",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionA"
    },
    {
        "question": "1+2=___",
        "optionA": "6",
        "optionB": "3",
        "optionC": "0",
        "optionD": "1",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 cows are eating some grass, 1 more cow joins them, how many total cows are there on the field",
        "optionA": "6",
        "optionB": "7",
        "optionC": "2",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionD"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 birds are sitting on a tree branch, 2 more birds join them",
        "optionA": "2",
        "optionB": "6",
        "optionC": "8",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    }
]

ch4=[
    {
        "question": "There are 6 jars, 4 of them break\nHow many jars are still left",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "5",
        "optionD": "9",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 4 books, Ashok takes 3 books away\nHow many books are left",
        "optionA": "9",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "1",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "7-5=___",
        "optionA": "6",
        "optionB": "2",
        "optionC": "0",
        "optionD": "1",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 cows are eating some grass, 1 cow leaves the field, how many total cows are there on the field",
        "optionA": "6",
        "optionB": "7",
        "optionC": "2",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 leaves are hanging on a branch, 4 of them fall\nHow many leaves are remaining on the tree",
        "optionA": "2",
        "optionB": "5",
        "optionC": "8",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    }
]

ch5=[
    {
        "question": "How many bananas can you see",
        "optionA": "13",
        "optionB": "14",
        "optionC": "10",
        "optionD": "18",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many ice-candies can you see",
        "optionA": "17",
        "optionB": "12",
        "optionC": "11",
        "optionD": "13",
        "correctoption": "optionC"
    },
    {
        "question": "13+5=___",
        "optionA": "16",
        "optionB": "18",
        "optionC": "10",
        "optionD": "19",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 10 match sticks, 8 more sticks are added to the bundle\nHow many match sticks are there now",
        "optionA": "16",
        "optionB": "17",
        "optionC": "12",
        "optionD": "18",
        "correctoption": "optionD"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 cars parked, 1 of them is driven\nHow many cars are still parked",
        "optionA": "2",
        "optionB": "5",
        "optionC": "8",
        "optionD": "3",
        "correctoption": "optionB"
    }
]


